Guide to the Hot Peaches Records MSS.420
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Recordings, 1971-2014; 5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, 1 cassette box, and 2 shared boxes.; 62 videocassettes (vhs); 50 audiocassettes; 2 sound tape reels; 14 videocassettes (u-matic); 12 videoreels (1/2 inch); 96.2 Gigabytes in 53 audio and video files
  - Untitled, Undated; ID: 420.0011 (Box 1, Vhs 420.0011)
- Series II. Scripts, 1964, 1972-2008; 1.50 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes.
  This series contains show scripts written by Jimmy Camicia between 1972 and the early 2000s, most of which were performed by Hot Peaches. Titles include Divas of Sheridan Square, Concentrated Camp, A Little Moonlight, and Death of a Handsome Man. This series also includes copyright documentation for a number of Camicia's scripts. Notated show scripts are located in Series III within show production work notebooks.
  - Crdule, June 16, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Sabled Fables, August 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Androgyny in Ostendorf, October 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Wonderful Wizard of U.S., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Scripts -- Copyright Registration Material, 1973-2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Alice of Scarsdale, February 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cinderella Brown, May 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - The Magic Hype, October 1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Midnight Mass, December 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The Watergate Scandals of '73, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - The Demented Diva, April 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hansel and Gretel, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Gay?, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Oscar, May 1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Murder in the Vatican, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Off-Off and Away, Summer 1979 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Petie and the Jewel, July 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - No Secrets, No Lies, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Waldorf Salad, December 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Away, March 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - A Christmas Card, Also Known As X-mas Cards, circa 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Last Brunch, April 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Richard's Predicament, May 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Telling Tales, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Concentrated Camp, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Heat, circa 1989-1990, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Fall of the Wall Revue (European Tour Version), April 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - La Dolce Peaches Cabaret, May 1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Farewell to Blush, November 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Nightbird, November 1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Ice Age / The Penguin, November 1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - The Mouth of God, November 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - The Death of a Handsome Man, August 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The Model (A Cartoon), September 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Three Small Men, October 1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Late Night Indulgences, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - The Tennessee Cat Clause, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - A Nite in Tennessee, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - The Short, Violent Life of Margie Good, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tulips and Cadavers (Revision), 2006 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Lamb Chops (Revision), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The Monroe Doctrine, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Amsterdam, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - A Little Moonlight, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Series III. Shows and Tours, 1971-2004; 6 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes and 1 flat-file folder.; 190 Megabytes in 1,485 computer files
  This series documents the process of producing Hot Peaches shows in New York City and Europe, dating from the early 1970s to the 2000s. Files in this series are organized by date and show title, with these files typically containing promotional fliers, show programs, and sheet music. Loose photographs in this series include promotional cast portraits, still images from shows, and backstage candid shots.
  Select shows in this series contain production work books which encompass the entire process of creating that show. These work books were created for a portion of the New York shows, but also more detailed work books for select European tours. Work books for the local productions typically contain notated scripts, cast lists, notes, stage directions, photographs, schedules, press clippings, brief journal entries, and costume and set sketches. European tour work book files contain much of the same material as the local production work books, with the addition of travel information and schedules. The series also contains a 1981 Master's thesis on the history of Hot Peaches written by a former cast member. Digital files containing photographs and text used on the Hot Peaches website from 2008-2009 are also in this series. Information on Hot Peaches cast member and gay liberation activist Marsha P Johnson can be found throughout this series dating from the 1970s until her death in the early 1990s. Show scripts without notations can be found in Series II.
  - Hot Screenland Whispers -- Hot Peaches Publication, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Fliers and Mailers, circa 1972-2004 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Photographs -- Cast Members, Shows, 1972-1998 (Box 8, Folder 9-11)
  - Androgyny in Ostendorf -- Sheet Music, October 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Alice and the Great American Side Show -- Promotional Material, January-February 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Cinderella Brown -- Sheet Music, Programs, Promotional Material, May 1973 (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
  - The Watergate Scandals of '73 -- Sheet Music, June-August 1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - The Magic Hype -- Sheet Music, Programs, Promotional Material, October-November 1973 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Alice -- Sheet Music, circa 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Demented Diva -- Sheet Music, Programs, Promotional Material, May 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  - Alice -- Program, June 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Wizard of Oz Parade and Wonderful Wizard of U.S. -- Promotional Flier, Program, August 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hansel and Gretel -- Promotional Material, Program, November 1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Show Reviews -- Press Clippings, 1974-1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Street Calls -- Program and Poster, March-April 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10, Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Sensual Savages -- Graphic Art for Show, June 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Sensual Savages -- Annotated Script, Promotional Material, Lyrics, June 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Ms. Hood -- Program, October-December 1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - The Divas of Sheridan Square -- Programs, Promotional Material, Booklet, Production Notes, Press Clipping, November 1975 (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
  - Merry Christmas, America -- Program, December 1975 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - The Divas of Sheridan Square (European Tour) -- Press Clippings, Promotional Material, Poster, Notated Script, Photographic Negatives of Show Graphics, April-November 1976 (Box 9, Folder 17-19, Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Transatlantic Cruise -- Promotional Material, Annotated Script, August 1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Gay? -- Promotional Flier, Show Production Images, January-August 1977 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
  - Oscar -- Promotional Material, Program, June 1978 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Parker, Ms. -- Promotional Material, Notated Script, Stage Directions, September 1978 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Oscar -- Sheet Music, circa 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Hot Peaches Logo Buttons and Name Tags, 1979, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Oscar (European Tour) -- Show Production Work Book, May-August 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Oscar (European Tour) -- Show Tickets, June 24, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Oscar (New York Performance) -- Cast Promotional Photograph, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Sheet Music for Songs / Lyrics Written by Jimmy Camicia, 1979-1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Break a Leg Gala Benefit for Ian McKay -- Notated Script, Stage Notes, May 25, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Hot Peaches: An Historical Study -- Masters Thesis by Linda Stein, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Valentine's Day Concert -- Images from Show, February 14, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - The Last Brunch -- Promotional Material, April 1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - The Heat (New York City) -- Show Work Book, June 1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - The Heat (New York City) -- Promotional Material, June 1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Concentrated Camp -- Show Work Book, December 1988-January 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11, Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - The Heat -- Sheet Music and Photographic Negatives from Performances, circa 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp Tour -- Pre-Tour Show Work Book, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp Tour -- Show Work Book, August-October 1989 (Box 11, Folder 6, Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp Tour -- Cast and Show Images, August-October 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp Tour -- Photographic Negative of Promotional Poster, August-October 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Heat and Concentrated Camp Tour -- Cast Promotional Images, August-October 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Chrysis' Heels: A Benefit for International Chrysis -- Benefit Promotional Material, Show Images, Notes, and a Memorial Program for Chrysis, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
  - European Summer Tour -- The Heat and Concentrated Camp Show Work Book, Summer 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - European Summer Tour -- The Heat and Concentrated Camp Promotional Poster (German), June 1990 (Flat-file-folder 20)
  - European Summer Tour -- The Heat and The Fall of the Wall Sheet Music, Summer 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - European Summer Tour -- The Heat Cast Photographs, Summer 1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - European Summer Tour -- The Fall of the Wall Promotional Material, Photographs, Small Album, Summer 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - European Summer Tour -- Concentrated Camp Program, Photographs, Summer 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Photographs -- Cast Members in Unknown Show, October 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - The Heat -- Show Work Book, Promotional Material, Marsha P. Johnson Portraits, February-March 1991 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
  - Non-Hot Peaches Shows and Events -- Programs, Photographs, 1991-2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Christopher Street Columbus -- Programs, Show Photographs and Slides, May 1992 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
  - Christopher Street Columbus Party -- German Poster, June 10, 1992 (Flat-file-folder 20)
  - Christopher Street Columbus -- Berlin Pre-Tour Work Book, June-August 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Christopher Street Columbus Tour -- Show Work Book, June-August 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
  - Christopher Street Columbus Tour -- Annotated Script, June-August 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Informational Sheet -- Brief History of Hot Peaches, circa 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Not Up to Snuff -- Program, August-September 1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Christopher Street Columbus Italy Tour -- Show Work Book, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Beyond Possessed -- Annotated Script, Promotional Material, Photographic Slides, April 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  - Europride Special Cabaret -- Promotional Programs, June 1994 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Beyond Possessed -- Show Work Book, Photographs, Promotional Material, August 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
  - The Heat and Beyond Possessed (European Tour) -- Show Work Book, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Beyond Possessed -- Sheet Music, Notes, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Late Night Indulgences -- Promotional Flier, Program, Photographic Slides, May-June 1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Play Genet -- Promotional Material, circa September 1997 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Play Genet -- Show Work Book, November 1997 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Play Genet -- Show Poems and Lyrics Booklet, 1997-1998, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Destiny and Desire -- Music Lyrics, March 1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - European Tour -- Play Genet Promotional Photographs, Show Work Book, Summer 1998 (Box 16, Folder 5-8)
  - Play Genet -- Program, September 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - A Nite in Tennessee: The Scat Queen of Atlanta -- Programs, July 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - The Short, Violent Life of Margie Good -- Show Work Book, Promotional Material, Show Still Photographs, April 2002 (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
  - Tulips and Cadavers -- Show Work Book, Promotional Material, Cast Promotional Images, Research Source Painting Images, March-April 2004 (Box 17, Folder 6-9)
  - Hot Peaches Website Files, 2008-2009; cuid39215 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_41)
  - Images -- Cast Members and Unknown Shows, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Sheet Music from Unidentified Shows, undated (Box 17, Folder 11-13)
  - Jimmy Camicia's Fabulous Valentine's Dance and Late Nite Revue -- Poster, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Series IV. Jimmy Camicia Writings, 1950s-2013; 9.50 Linear Feet in 20 manuscript boxes and 1 small flat box.
  This series contains personal journals, writings, and books written by Jimmy Camicia (also known earlier in his career as Jimmy Centola). This series also contains Bard College publications from the mid-1960s, including Gesamtwerk and Bard Psychology Journal of which Camicia served as editor and writer. Other published material in this series includes a poetry book The Divas of Sheridan Square which Camicia eventually adapted into a Hot Peaches show, and his 2013 book My Dear, Sweet Self: A Hot Peach Life which recounts Camicia's early life and the history of Hot Peaches. This series also contains articles written by Camicia about his experiences performing and traveling in Europe with the Hot Peaches cast. His loose poetry and a mock-up of a children's book are also in this series. Documentation related to Camicia's struggle with his landlord to maintain his rent-controlled apartment in New York provides insight into the struggles facing an artist and his housing issues during the 1980s and 1990s. This series also contains a small collection of Camicia's correspondence from the mid-1970s and 1990s.
  An extensive collection of Camicia's journals are in this series dating from the 1950s to 2012 that often contain not only diary entries, but photographs; press clippings; sketches of portraits, costumes, and sets; and writing notes and ideas. These journals explore Camicia's early life while still in school, traveling in Europe as a young man, the development of Hot Peaches, relationships with cast members, and critiques on Hot Peaches shows. These journals also document the viewpoint of a gay performer and writer living in New York during the 1970s-2000s, as well as the experimental theater scene, the gay community in the West Village, and the drag and gay club scenes.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged by item type and chronologically within those groupings.
  - Scrapbook -- Jimmy Camicia and Hot Peaches, 1950s-1979 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook -- Diary Entries, School Ephemera, Sketches, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Journal -- Diary Entries, Photographs, Postcards, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Diaries / Journals, 1965-1969 (Box 20, Folder 2-4, Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Journals -- Diary Entries, Addresses, Writings, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 5, Box 21, Folder 1-3)
  - Journal -- The Pitts Book, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Journals -- Diary Entries, Addresses, Writings, Sketches, 1974-1977 (Box 21, Folder 4-5, Box 22, Folder 1, Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Journal -- Diary Entries and Script for Legend of Lola LaMarr, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Journals -- Diary Entries, Addresses, Writings, 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 3-5, Box 23, Folder 1-4, Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Journals -- Diary Entries, Addresses, Writings, 1980-1987 (Box 24, Folder 2-4, Box 25, Folder 1-4, Box 26)
  - Journal / Diary -- Mexico Trip, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Journal -- Diary Entries, Appointments, Addresses, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
  - Journal -- Ondine Writing Project, Diary Entries, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Journal -- Daily Diary Entries, European "Tour Book" Diary, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Journal -- Diary Entries, Appointments, Addresses, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 2-4, Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Journal -- London, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Journal -- Diary Entries, Addresses, 1992-1994 (Box 29, Folder 3-4, Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Journal -- Tour Diary, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Journals / Diaries, 1994-1996, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 3-4, Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Journal -- Diary Entries, Writings, Demimonde Play Manuscript, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Journal -- Diary Entries, Addresses, Writings, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Journal -- "Gilles and Pierre" Writings, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Journals / Diaries, 1998-2001 (Box 32, Folder 1-5, Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Journals / Diaries, 2001-2007 (Box 34, Folder 1-4, Box 35)
  - Journals / Diaries, 2007-2012, undated (Box 36, Folder 1-4, Box 37)
  - Bard College Publication -- Gesamtwerk, circa 1960s (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Bard College Publication -- Bard Psychology Journal, December 1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Poems, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Booklet -- The Divas of Sheridan Square, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Mouth of the Dragon: 8 -- Jimmy Centola Poetry Contributor, March 1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Poem -- "The Queen of Time", 1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1978, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
  - Work Book -- Apartment Issues Documentation, 1980-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9, Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Article and Draft -- Mary, It was Fab or Concentrating Camp: Touring Europe with the Hot Peaches, November 13, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Article -- Notes from the Fallen Wall, October 1, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Article -- Drag, Glorious Drag, February 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Poem -- "Thanksgiving", December 1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Poetry added to found antique ledger, 1995 (Box 41)
  - Sketchbook, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Booklet -- Poems for Drag Queens, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Book and Promotional Card-- My Dear, Sweet Self: A Hot Peach Life, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Card with Camicia Drawing, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Poem -- "The Midnight Poem", undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Poem -- "Demented Darling", undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - ABC -- Mock-up for Children's Book, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Collage with Magazine Images, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Series B-D Material
  - Divas of Sheridan Square, New York City -- Part I, 1975 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_12)
  - Divas of Sheridan Square, New York City -- Part II, 1975 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_13)
  - An Evening with Sister Tooey, The Loft, 1979 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_14)
  - The Last Brunch, Theater for the New City, New York, April 1985 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_15)
  - The Heat, June 18, 1988 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_16)
  - The Heat, Theater for the New City, New York, June 18, 1988 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_17)
  - Harvest Moon Cabaret Benefit for Concentrated Camp Tour, Soho Gallery, 1988 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_18)
  - Harvest Moon Cabaret Benefit for Concentrated Camp Tour, Soho Gallery, circa 1988 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_19)
  - The Heat Compilation -- Theater for the New City, New York (1988); Tempodrom, Berlin (1989); Specks Film, Berlin (1989), 1988-1989 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_20)
  - Chrysis Heels Benefit, La Mama Club, February 20, 1990 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_21)
  - Chrysis Heels Benefit, La Mama Club -- Exerpts, February 20, 1990 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_22)
  - Chrysis Heels Benefit, La Mama Club -- Rehearsal, Backstage, Performance, February 20, 1990 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_23)
  - Chrysis Heels Benefit, La Mama Club -- Tony, February 20, 1990 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_24)
  - Concentrated Camp, East Berlin, Summer 1990 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_25)
  - Concentrated Camp, East Berlin, Summer 1990 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_26)
  - Harvest Moon Ball, Theater for the New City, New York, November 24, 1990 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_27)
  - Split '92 film by E. Turk, on Performer International Chrysis, 1992 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_28)
  - Peaches in Parts -- Documentary on Hot Peaches, circa 1998 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_29)
  - Peaches in Parts -- Documentary on Hot Peaches, circa 1998 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_30)
  - Peaches in Parts -- Documentary on Hot Peaches, circa 1998 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_31)
  - Peaches in Parts -- Documentary on Hot Peaches, circa 1998 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_32)
  - Hot Peach Film 1973, Hot Peach Retrospective 1973-1998, circa 1998 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_33)
  - 1974 Hot Peaches Movie, circa 1998 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_34)
  - Entr'Acte -- Meeting, Script Reading?, May 27, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_35)
  - Entr'Acte -- Meeting, Script Reading?, May 27, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_36)
  - Entr'Acte -- Meeting, Script Reading?, May 27, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_37)
  - The Tony Fish Show, July 12, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_38)
  - Footage on Each Cast Member -- Hot Peaches Les Boys; Hot Peaches Our Queens; Hot Peach Women, October 19, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_39)
  - Footage on Each Cast Member -- Hot Peaches Les Boys; Hot Peaches Our Queens; Hot Peach Women, October 26, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_40)
  - Footage on Each Cast Member -- Hot Peaches Les Boys; Hot Peaches Our Queens; Hot Peach Women, October 26, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_41)
  - Movie -- Pay It No Mind: Marsha P. Johnson -- Screening at IFC Cinema, Pre-Show Interviews, November 28, 2011 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_42)
  - Movie -- Pay It No Mind: Marsha P. Johnson, circa 2011 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_43)
  - Movie --Pay It No Mind: Marsha P. Johnson -- 1992 Interviews with Marsha P. Johnson, Friends, Hot Peaches Castmembers Used in Film, circa 2011 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_44)
  - Hot Peaches Cast Members -- Still Photographs, February 2014 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_45)
  - Hot Peaches Cast Member Wilhelmina Ross -- Still Photographs and Video Clips from Shows, undated (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_46)
  - "Brothers -- Jim, Joe Pete" -- Footage of Apartment Interior, undated (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_420_ER_47)